I've always been drawn to beautiful things.
So how do you solve this equation?
Rainbows sparkling after the rain.
Coming-of-age movies
about friendship and romance.
First, you add the two equations,
which cancels out "y."
Middle School
Mathematics
But even these don't come close
to the beauty of flowers.
One day, when I have my own store,
I want to grow my own flowers.
Making flower accessories is
how I bring my passion to life.
Middle School
Mathematics
Shoot.
Yu! Let's eat lunch!
What're you in a hurry for?
Lemme guess, you couldn't wait to see me?
You like me way too much!
Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
A Hunk and Morning Glory Yukata
H-Hey, so...
I was thinking of eating by myself tod—
Drink up!
Pressuring me in silence.
"The world's cutest girl came to find you."
"Stop moping around and let's get going."
Something like that.
I'll admit, she is cute.
Yo, Himari!
Let's eat together for a change.
Wait, you're still hanging out with him?
Don't you get tired of that loser?
You'd be surprised!
Yu's actually super smooth!
Yeah, right.
We're going to karaoke after school.
You should come.
As much as I'd love to belt it out, I dunno.
You did send me those messages yesterday.
Excuse me? What messages?
I can explain!
Let's go, Yu!
H-Hey, Himari!
So... I've been meaning to ask you.
You've been avoiding me lately, haven't you?
I-I dunno what you're talking about.
Come on, spill.
F-Fine. You win!
What is it? Did I do something?
You haven't done anything!
Then why?
U-Um...
Himari-san, there's this
thing called "class."
What do you mean?
You know, um...
You're too nice, Yu.
Don't pay attention to those guys.
You don't even know them.
You knew the other guys were bad-mouthing me?
They bug me about it, too.
Did they tell you to
stop hanging out with me?
They say you're out of my league.
And why would you care what they think?
Well I can't just ignore it.
Besides, you have your friends...
in the popular crowd.
I don't want to hold you back.
Here, look. It's from that guy back there.
Himari, will you go out with me?
I like you a lot.
He's been at it for a month now.
Seriously.
I'll break up with my girlfriend.
And this is from his girlfriend.
She thinks I've been trying
to steal him from her.
Jeez...
Dating's no joke.
I'm tired of getting dragged
into it, you know?
That was a good lunch.
Anyways, my point is...
You may think the popular crowd's
friendship and romance
is this grand, beautiful thing.
But "beautiful" doesn't always mean "pure."
I'd rather have things
be pure, not beautiful.
That's why I like how genuine
your eyes get when you work.
Your passion isn't beneath me at all.
So promise me, you'll be
my best friend forever.
And that you'll never fall for me.
Well, duh.
I'm your...
b-best friend, after all.
Gotcha.
I'm your... b-best friend, after all.
Himari!
Bwa-ha!
You suck! Delete that!
I don't think so!
Get back here!
How about this?
From now on, when guys come on to me,
I'll tell them that we're dating.
Don't drag me into
the popular crowd's feuds.
I don't need any more crap from those guys.
Besides, what if they believe you?
Then wanna actually go out?
No way.
The last thing I'd want
is to go out with you.
Bwa-ha!
See, you know me too well.
Cool, thanks.
We should go back like this.
Come on, let's go!
W-Wait!
Two years later, spring of junior year...
Himari, your lunch!
Whoops, my bad!
I ended up falling for Himari.
Apparently, Himari's not
going to Tokyo anymore.
And I totally missed my chance
to tell her how I feel.
I just need to play it cool.
Hey, Yu! Morning!
'Sup, Himari? Morning.
Ew, what's with the creepy smile?
You have a stomach ache or something?
Don't be a hater.
That was a hunky smile.
I dunno about hunky.
Kinda looked like you had an upset stomach.
Whatever.
Where's your ring?
Oh, that? Right here.
I figured wearing a ring
to school might be a bit much.
Yeah, true.
Hey, want me to replace that belt?
Nope, I like this one.
It's the first piece you ever gave me.
C-Cool.
I was this close to saying,
"You're so cute I could die, and I love you."
Good thing her cheesy
line snapped me out of it.
Either way, thank goodness...
I figured she slept on it and decided
she didn't want the ring anymore.
Don't tell me you were afraid I slept on it
and decided I didn't want the ring anymore?
Yikes!
Yu, you just can't get enough of me!
If you like me so much,
wanna actually go out?
Screw you! Don't underestimate me.
I was prepared to quit school, you know.
Hey, Himari.
I realized that you're the only one for me.
If you're really up for it,
would you go out with me?
Perfect, now for the finisher...
Just kidding!
I got you, didn't I?
Whatever.
I'm sorry, I got too cocky.
You think you can trick me
with a phony spiel like that?
Oh yeah.
Go on, I'll catch up with you.
That was a close call!
Jeez, Yu. He almost got me.
For a split second,
I thought he was for real.
I missed the chance to tell him
that people know he's the creator of You.
Or about Enocchi...
Hii-chan, I'm never speaking to you again.
There you are.
Natsume, stop by the teacher's office.
You turned in your midterm
exams completely blank?!
Keep your voice down!
Not totally blank. I think
I answered a couple questions.
But I was so tired, I fell asleep.
What happened?
I was so focused on making that piece.
Oh... that's why?
They're letting me retake
the exam this Sunday.
If I pass every subject,
they'll let me off the hook.
We still have some time until Sunday.
It's okay, I'll help you study after school.
Thanks.
By the way, this may not be
the best time but...
What's up?
People found out that you're behind You.
Is that bad?
It's not like I was
hiding my face on social media.
Shouldn't you be more worried?
Why? I don't see any issue with it.
I do!
If people find out you
make those cute accessories,
you'll have a flock of girls around you!
What are you talking about?
What if what happened
with Enocchi happens again?
Girls could come up to you and ask to model,
and you'll go along with it like last time.
Could you not bring that up again?
Listen, Himari.
I'll say it again.
Yeah, what?
This ring belongs to you and you only.
As long as you keep this,
you're my number one model.
A-Aww, you really can't get... get enough...
Ow!
Why did you smack me?!
I heard something pop!
You're being way too cheesy, that's why!
Doesn't give you the right to slap me!
I-It was your fault.
'S-Sup, Enomoto-san?
Taking a break.
R-Right.
H-How long have you been
there? I didn't notice.
From when Hii-chan yelled
about girls flocking to you.
Sorry to bother you.
Y-Yu, did something happen with Enocchi?
I could ask you the same.
She's totally avoiding you.
Actually, a lot did happen.
While Himari and I were fighting.
But I can't say that.
Honestly, the leak is
a bigger issue than the exams.
Yu
Himari
Enocchi
It's pretty clear who started it.
I'll keep Yu to myself as his best friend.
And write my own happy ending!
No matter what gets in the way.
You're quicker than I expected.
Why did you leak that stuff
about You, after all this time?
Is it not obvious?
It's all to help Rin-chan beat you!
No remorse. What an ass!
Too bad, but Yu's my best friend.
I like Enocchi, but even if
she cuts me off, I won't give that up.
You're so desperate.
Anyone could tell how you feel about him.
Hate to break it to you,
but this won't go your way.
Yu chose me, and he's loyal—
Let me be very clear.
If you really wanted Natsu for yourself,
you should've taken him to Tokyo.
Natsu was prepared to leave everything
for you and you weren't.
You decided not to take him
while you had the chance.
What are you talking about?
You'll see soon enough.
Sorry, but you're not even a threat to us.
So how exactly do I study for a make-up exam?
I dunno, but I messaged Onii-chan about it.
I'm sure he'll know what to do.
I can't believe you haven't
visited my place in almost a year.
Yeah, since the start of freshman year.
Himari Inuzuka
(My Granddaughter)
Yu Natsume
(My Grandson-in-Law)
Congratulations on
entering high school!
That banner your grandpa made
was so embarrassing.
Oh yeah. Grandpa's staying
in the hospital right now.
And Mom's giddy to spend the night
with Dad while he's back in Japan.
So I guess it's just us today.
Take that!
Ow!
I'm not falling for that one.
You said Hibari-san would be here.
I gotta say hi.
Onii-chan isn't here either.
But you said he'd help me study.
He sent over a big pile of
notes and some old practice books.
So I'm gonna help you study
while looking them over.
Onii-chan's too busy
with work to be here himself.
Oh, okay.
So wait, we're seriously gonna be alone?
Hello, Yu-kun!
Welcome back home!
Bwa-ha!
Himari!
Now, let's get to work.
Hibari-san, what about work?
No worries.
I served up one of my staff
to attend today's conference.
Served up?
Yu-kun.
Y-Yes!
I've always been in agreement with Himari.
You shine the brightest
when making accessories.
I believe your work will make this
town known across the globe one day.
W-Wow, thanks.
Which is exactly why I can't
allow anything to get in your way!
Like studying for exams, for example!
S-Sure, but I'm a student.
It can't be helped.
There's a way to get out of that.
This is your chance to master everything
there is to know in high school.
That way, you'll never have to study
for an exam ever again.
In fact, I could help you
enter Japan's best institution!
H-Himari!
Y-You said you'd study with me!
There's no stopping Onii-chan
when he gets fired up like this.
Good luck, Yu!
Let's study with your brother-in-law.
Th-Thanks.
Yu, hop in the bath while it's hot.
Sorry about Onii-chan.
He's been real busy lately.
I thought he could use
that to blow off some steam.
It's okay, I'm the one
who should be thanking him.
You sacrificed me on purpose?
Bwa-ha!
A beauty in a yukata...
What accessory would pair well?
Something around her neck?
Yu, you're staring.
Oh, sorry.
I was just thinking of what
accessories would go with that yukata.
I didn't say you can't stare.
Cut it out!
Wow, it's like a real hot springs inn!
I've visited a few times, but
I've never stayed the night or taken a bath.
You'll be here again tomorrow anyways.
Go ahead and leave your
clothes in the hamper.
I'll have our helpers wash it.
Really? Thanks!
Which seat has Himari used?
Hold up, what am I thinking?
Am I stupid?
Heads up, Yu, I'm opening the door.
Bwa-ha!
Such a virgin.
Shut up!
I've never had a girl see me naked!
Why did you open the door?
You know, you worked so hard today.
Want me to wash your back for you?
This girl is out of her mind!
Since I couldn't help you study,
maybe you could use some cheering up.
Th-That's weird between opposite genders.
Yeah, but we're best friends.
Or do you actually see me as more than that?
She's just teasing me like usual.
I'm not falling for it.
Fine. Could you, please?
O-Okay.
Then let me undress.
Huh?
Turn around so you can't see, okay?
But she's just washing my back.
There's no need to undress...
Wait, that's beside the point.
Himari-san? Don't you think
that's a bit overboard?
Yu, keep your eyes closed.
O-Okay!
"Okay"?
It's the same arms as the science room...
I can't!
Come on, let me wash you down.
No!
Bwa-ha!
Himari!
I didn't think it would actually
go exactly as Himari imagined.
Hibari-san, that wasn't funny.
You're right, I'm sorry.
But goodness, are you two
always fooling around like this?
Uh, well, you see...
I always try and stop her.
I mean—nothing's ever happened!
I have no right judging
how you two act as best friends.
Anyways, I'm glad you two worked things out.
Huh?
I know what happened.
Why wouldn't I know?
That's definitely convincing.
I was worried Himari
wouldn't be able to apologize.
She's been too spoiled growing up.
Himari apologize? For what?
I thought Himari apologized yesterday.
That's how you two made up, right?
Um, we did make up, but...
Himari never did anything wrong.
I was the one who apologized.
It was my fault.
What?
She hasn't apologized.
Hibari-san?
Do you mind sharing a bit more on that?
My bad, Himari. Didn't mean to out you.
Oh my gosh, that was crazy!
If Onii-chan hadn't walked by,
Yu and I would have been in our bath alone!
Romance sure does take a toll...
But I don't mind, I guess.
When Yu claps back like that,
there's this weird tension in the air.
It's almost like a thrill, it's so exciting.
Was I a masochist all along?
Is that Yu?
Oh my gosh, he came to
a girl's room this late at night!
Could this mean...?
If he's up for it, so am I!
Come in!
It'd make things weirder
if I pushed him away, right?
Himari, let's have a little chat.
Shall we?
Yu-kun, when it comes
to studying, repetition is key.
You got a pretty good
grasp of things yesterday,
so let's take mock exams as many
times as possible until Sunday.
O-Okay.
Thank you. By the way...
And another thing.
Lack of sleep is your biggest enemy.
Feel free to use my
favorite relaxation items.
G-Great.
The Inuzuka Family specialty:
kill them with kindness.
See you tonight.
Thank you.
Himari, you okay?
Yeah, now that Onii-chan's gone.
I'm better now.
Yu-kun.
Good morning.
H-Hey, Enomoto-san...
'S-Sup, Enocchi?
Is she some kind of modern ninja?
Yu-kun, did you just get
out of a car with Hii-chan?
U-Um, Hibari-san was just dropping us off.
I stayed at Himari's place last nigh—
You stayed at Hii-chan's house?
Um, it's nothing. No big deal.
I was studying with
Hibari-san the entire time.
Studying? For what?
I have to retake my exams on Sunday.
I can't move to the next
grade without passing.
Then I'll come, too.
I'll stay the night, too!
The Scent of Cherry Sage